cjbanks.com 2017-06-06

# Christopher & Banks | cjbanks Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) was last updated in July 2016 (“Effective Date”).

Thank you for visiting the Privacy Policy for the Christopher & Banks family of companies. We want you to know that privacy issues are important to us. We will only use your information as permitted by this Privacy Policy as it may be amended from time to time. For further information please contact us as described below.

We want you to know: (i) what information we gather; (ii) the steps we take to protect the information that you provide us; (iii) how we use that information; (iv) when we share it with others; and (v) that we periodically review and revise this Privacy Policy.

**By doing business with us, including via our Website at[christopherandbanks.com](http://www.christopherandbanks.com/returnsexchange.html "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel") (the “Website”) or interacting with Christopher & Banks in the manner described in this Privacy Policy at any time after the Effective Date, you consent to this Privacy Policy.**

Specifically, you:

  * consent to the application of this Privacy Policy to you and to the terms and practices described herein; 
  * consent to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Policy; and
  * acknowledge and agree that we may change, modify or otherwise amend this Policy from time-to-time.

This Privacy Policy applies to the Christopher & Banks family of companies, which is comprised of Christopher & Banks, Inc. and all of our current and future parents, subsidiaries and affiliates (meaning corporations under the same control, to which we may refer as “Legal Affiliates”, and collectively with Christopher & Banks, Inc., as “we”, “us”,“our”, “Christopher & Banks”, and the “Company”) and to include our Website which is operated with the assistance of certain third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other companies or websites, and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of websites operated by others, even if they are linked to our Website. This Privacy Policy specifically does not apply to businesses that we may refer to as “Marketing Affiliates”, “marketing partners”, “third party partners” or “vendors”, all of which are unrelated to us.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect a variety of information about our in-store and online customers and Website visitors. This section describes the information we collect. The information you provide may be used by the Company in our retail business, our online business, to fulfill orders, to operate our loyalty program and our private label credit card program and to communicate with customers regarding offers of goods, promotions or other benefits from us or our third party partners that Christopher & Banks reasonably believes may be of interest to all or certain of our customers based upon customer demographics, buying history or other reasons. _Information Collected Automatically_. Each time a computer or other device (collectively, a “computer”) visits our Website, we may automatically collect certain information from that computer. Information that is automatically collected may include (but is not limited to) the following: 

  * characteristics about your browser, operating system and computer you use to access our website
  * the name of the domain and host from which the computer accessed the Internet;
  * the Internet address of any website from which the computer linked;
  * the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using;
  * the date and time the computer accessed the Website; and
  * if you accessed our Website via a link in an email you received from Christopher & Banks, your email address,

This type of information on its own does not tell us who you are, although it may identify the computer that you are using and how you are using it. We may also combine this information with personal information you have provided to us (as described below).

Also, we may place a file or files called a “cookie”or “pixel on computers that visit our Website. These are small data files that receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us through your computer or mobile device. We may also use “web beacons,” which are clear image files that may be placed on a website to monitor the behavior of visiting users of the website. Web beacons and cookies may be used by us and our marketing partners to allow your computer to use all the features on our Website and to customize your experience. You may enable, disable, block or remove some types of cookies and related files on your computer by following the instructions on your Web browser. While cookies are not required to view our Website, they are necessary in order for most functions on our site to work, and therefore we recommend allowing their use. For example, without cookies enabled you will be unable to log in, make a purchase, or view your account. We use cookies for a variety of purposes, including to populate information for returning visitors who have logged into our site to give them access to personalized features and settings. We also may use cookies to recognize customer traffic patterns and site use. This information can help us improve the site’s layout and design, including the features and personalization that we can offer returning users.

On our Website, we also collect and track certain types of information about your use of our Website, such as which pages or features of our Website you visit, when and how often. We may combine this type of information with other demographic information about you or other information you provide to us.

We use a third-party service to publish ads on our behalf across the Internet. This third-party service may collect information about your visits to our Website and other websites and your interaction with our products and services, as well as with websites generally. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. They also enable us to collect the following types of information: pages visited, products viewed and/or purchased, search term usage and other common website metrics. This information helps us to learn things like what pages are most attractive to our customers, which of our products most interest our customers and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. This is often called “behavioral advertising.” This information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by many websites. Our Website does not respond to “do not track” requests from browsers, but several of our third party service providers who utilize these tracking technologies on or Website may enable you to opt out of these advertising practices. To learn more about these advertising practices or to opt out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/ "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel") or [aboutads.info/choices/.](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel") We also provide you with additional tools to opt out of marketing from us as explained below.

Personal Information that You Choose to Provide to Us. You may provide us information about yourself through our Website, in person, in a store, by our store personnel using point of sale systems, by phone or mail, through social networking and similar websites, by e-mail or text messages, and in other ways. For example, you will give us information if you place an order; create a user profile, provide requested information as part of a loyalty program, credit card application or employment application, or a registration either online or in-store; request information from us; send us an e-mail or text message; provide feedback about our stores or website; send us your name or other information; enter a contest or sweepstakes either online or in-store; follow or interact with us on social media; or fill out certain forms related to our business of selling women’s clothing or in response to a marketing program or other promotion that we may be involved in. The information that you provide to us may include your name, address, telephone number, purchase information and history, e-mail address, and credit card number, as well as other information. You may also provide us with the name and address of a gift recipient. 

If you apply for a Christopher & Banks credit card online, you will be providing your Personal Information directly to the issuing bank for the Christopher & Banks credit card. However, your name, address, phone number, birth date and credit card number, as well as any additional information necessary for us to provide you with the perks and privileges of the Christopher & Banks credit card, may be provided to us by the card issuer.

Your full name in connection with one or more of the following pieces of information is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Personal Information”: your mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, or credit card number. Although you are not required to provide us with any Personal Information, if you decline to do so you may not be able to perform certain actions, such as completing an order, ordering a gift card, applying for a Christopher & Banks credit card, or joining any loyalty or reward program that we might offer.

From time-to-time, we may supplement the information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or demographic information based on your zip code. We may also supplement the information you give us with information we collect from you in other ways. For example, if you shop at one of our stores, we may supplement the information you provide online with information we collect at the store. In this Privacy Policy, we refer collectively to Personal Information and other information about you as “information.”

In this Privacy Policy, we refer collectively to Personal Information and other information about you as “information.”

WHY DO WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We may collect your information:

  * for the purposes described in this or future versions of this Privacy Policy;
  * as permitted or required by applicable law, regulation, court order or legal process; and
  * for any additional purposes for which we have obtained your consent.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?

As stated above, we and third parties may use your information to help us make the Website more useful to you and for other business purposes. For example, we or our Marketing Affiliates may learn how many computers visited our Website or what pages were most popular. We and/or our Marketing Affiliates may prepare reports and analyses using such information.

We may combine this information with Personal Information and use and share the combined information in the ways described in this Privacy Policy.

Personal Information. We may use your Personal Information in order to manage, maintain, and develop our operations, including for example:

  * to establish, maintain and manage our relationship with you so that we may provide you with the items that you have ordered; 
  * to enable you to register and access an account with us;
  * to be able to review your orders so that we may: (i) understand your preferences for our products; and (ii) work to improve our Website and products;
  * to analyze what items you may be most interested in and suggest those items to you;
  * to communicate with you, and to send you information we think may be of interest to you, including marketing information from ourselves and/or our third party partners;
  * to protect us against error, fraud, theft and damage to our goods and property; 
  * to enable us to comply with applicable law, regulation, court order or legal process; and
  * any other reasonable purpose to which you consent. 

WHEN DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We may share your information with selected third parties: 

  * as described in this and any future versions of this Privacy Policy;
  * as permitted or required by applicable law, regulation, court order or legal process;
  * as part of our regular reporting activities;
  * to protect our rights and property;
  * during emergency situations or where we deem it necessary to protect the safety of a person or group of persons; and
  * with your consent.

We also may share your information with selected third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we share your information with the Marketing Affiliates that we hire to operate our Website, receive and fulfill orders, provide customer support and other support services, collect feedback about our stores and Website, assist us in the administration of our loyalty program, send emails, mailings or catalogs for us, market our products or services, or perform other services for us. In such cases, we will direct the Marketing Affiliate to use and protect the information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy to the extent we are able to do so. Our Marketing Affiliates are not authorized to use your information for any purposes other than to provide services to us. As stated above, the term “we” includes the Christopher & Banks family of companies, each member of which may therefore use and share the information as permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

In addition, from time-to-time we may share your information or our mailing lists (both postal mail and e-mail) with marketing partners that may jointly with us or independently contact you or market to you. We also may utilize service providers to assist us in aggregating customer information. We may then share such aggregated information with prospective marketing partners and advertisers. We will direct marketing partners and advertisers to use and protect the information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

When Christopher & Banks conducts contests, sweepstakes, promotions and surveys, or joins with other companies to do so, if you choose to participate you may be asked to provide Personal Information. Christopher & Banks and the other participating companies may use this information for such purposes as notifying winners and fulfilling promotional obligations, and may also cross reference customer databases to identify common customers. Information from these activities may be used to explore future promotional opportunities or fulfill contractual obligations with respect to such contests, sweepstakes, etc.

Further, as we are a U.S.-based company and your Personal Information will generally be stored in our offices and with our service providers in the United States, such Personal Information will be subject to the laws of the government of the United States of America. 

OPTING IN AND OUT FOR ADVERTISING AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS

As stated above, we and third parties acting on our behalf may contact you and market to you, including by e-mail, Internet connection, text, telephone, fax or mail, consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable law. We permit you to opt out of promotional and marketing communications as follows. Our various communication lists are administered separately, so it is necessary to opt out of each separately; opting out of one form of communication does not automatically opt you out from others. We expect and direct third parties with whom we share your information (other than third parties providing support services only on our behalf) to also allow you to opt out of future e-mail and texting marketing communications. Participation in certain of our programs, including any loyalty program, may require you to accept e-mail communications regarding the program itself. 

E–mail: : To opt out of receiving promotional e-mail communications, click the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the e-mail that you receive or email [customerservice@christopherandbanks.com](mailto:customerservice@christopherandbanks.com "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel"). 

Text Messages: You will only receive promotional text messages from Christopher & Banks if you expressly opt in to receive such messages. If you would like to stop receiving promotional text messages from Christopher & Banks, reply to a text message you receive from us with the word “STOP”.

Postal Mail and Phone: You may opt out of receiving phone calls and mailings by postal mail by contacting us as described in “Our Contact Information” below. 

It may take us a number of days to complete the process to remove you from our communication distribution lists, as is permitted by law. 

If you do not want us to share any of your Personal Information with third parties (other than our service providers or as required by law), please contact us at Customer Service, Christopher & Banks, Inc., 2400 Xenium Lane North, Plymouth, Minnesota 55441 or [customerservice@christopherandbanks.com](mailto:customerservice@christopherandbanks.com "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel") and we will remove you from our database. Taking certain actions after making such a request, such as placing an order or signing up for our loyalty program, will result in you being added back to our database, and as a result, your Personal Information may be shared with third parties as described in this Privacy Policy

OUR OWNERSHIP OF INFORMATION

Our record of all your information is an asset of ours and belongs to us. In the event of a sale, merger, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation, corporate reorganization, grant of a security interest, or similar transaction involving some or all of our business, we may share with or transfer your information to the buyer, creditor or successor entity. Because one of the purposes for which Christopher & Banks collects, uses and/or discloses Personal Information is the operation of its business, in the event that all or part of the assets of Christopher & Banks are sold to a new owner, all Personal Information, or that part of the Personal Information associated with the assets being sold, will be transferred (disclosed) to the new owners, subject to applicable laws . We may also continue to retain a copy of that Personal Information.

SECURITY

Your information is stored on servers located in the United States. We and the vendors who help us with hosting and security use a number of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that are intended to be appropriate to the sensitivity of the personal information in question. However, there is no such thing as perfect security. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Website, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Website, and you do so at your own risk. You understand and agree that we are not responsible for the unlawful actions of third parties or the consequences of such actions. You should take your own steps to protect your own computer systems and data from viruses, hackers, identity thieves and other risks.

We use the industry standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) in an effort to keep your order information secure. SSL encryption has been established for every transaction made through our Websites.

The security of your Personal Information is important to us; please advise us at [ privacy@christopherandbanks.com](mailto:privacy@christopherandbanks.com "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel") immediately of any incident involving the loss of, unauthorized access to, or disclosure of Personal Information that is in our custody or control.

HOW DO I VIEW OR REVISE MY INFORMATION?

Our Website may permit you to view and change portions of your Personal Information, such as your shipping and billing addresses, telephone number, birthday and password if you have an account on our Website. Click [here](https://www.christopherandbanks.com/account "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel") to view or change this contact information. You may also contact us in the ways described below in the section on Our Contact Information to change some portions of your Personal Information, or, to the extent required by law, to learn what type of Personal Information is being kept about you.

When requesting access to your Personal Information, please note that we may request specific information from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access, as well as to search for and provide you some of the Personal Information that we hold about you. If you require assistance in preparing your request, please contact [ privacy@christopherandbanks.com](mailto:privacy@christopherandbanks.com "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel").

Please note the following:

  * in some circumstances, we may not agree with your request to change your Personal Information and will instead append an alternative text to the record in question 
  * even if you change your Personal Information, we may continue to preserve a copy of your old information based on various back-up and archival methods in place at Christopher & Banks;
  * your right to access the personal information that we hold about you is not absolute. There are some instances where applicable law or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide some or all of the Personal Information that we hold about you. In addition, your Personal Information may have been destroyed, erased, or made anonymous or unavailable in accordance with our security, record retention or other practices. 

WHAT ABOUT PRIVACY ON OTHER SITES?

Our Website may contain links to other web sites. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of web sites operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other websites is subject to the terms and conditions of those websites, including the privacy policies of those websites.

If you are visiting our Website through a link from another website or search engine, information about your visit to us may be collected by the provider of the other website or search engine. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these other websites or search engines.

NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS/YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a resident of the State of California, you may request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed your Personal Information during the preceding calendar year for the third parties’ marketing purposes. 

To request such a list, you should send a request to [ privacy@christopherandbanks.com](mailto:privacy@christopherandbanks.com "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel") or Attn: Privacy, Christopher & Banks, Inc., 2400 Xenium Lane North, Plymouth, MN 55441. Please include “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line of your email or on the mailing envelope of your request, and include your name and mailing address. 

PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Policy on our Website. You may wish to check this section of our Website from time to time, because by visiting our Website, you agree to accept any such changes to this Privacy Policy.

VISITORS FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATESS

Your information is being sent to and used by us in the United States and Canada and may pass through servers located in the United States.

SPECIAL RULES ABOUT CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

We will not intentionally collect online any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 may use our Website only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. If you think that we have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us as described below and we will delete it from our files.

LAST UPDATE

This Privacy Policy was last updated in July 2016.

INTERPRETATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Any interpretation of this Privacy Policy will be made by management of Christopher & Banks in its sole discretion. This Privacy Policy includes examples but is not intended to be restricted in its application to such examples; therefore where the word “including” is used, it shall mean “including without limitation.” 

This Privacy Policy does not create or confer upon any individual any rights, or impose upon us any rights or obligations outside of, or in addition to, any rights or obligations imposed by United States or Canadian privacy laws, as applicable. Should there be, in a specific case, any inconsistency between this Privacy Policy and such privacy laws, this Privacy Policy shall be interpreted, in that specific case, to give effect to and comply with applicable privacy laws.

OUR CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or desire to register a concern or complaint, please contact us in any of three ways:

  1. 1.Send us an e-mail: [ privacy@christopherandbanks.com](mailto:privacy@christopherandbanks.com "Christopher & Banks® | cj banks® Missy, Petite and Women's Apparel");
  2. 2.Call us at: (763) 551-5000; or
  3. 3.Write to us at: Attn: Privacy, Christopher & Banks, Inc., 2400 Xenium Lane North, Plymouth, Minnesota 55441.
